<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tips To Travel</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main3">Main3Activity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="about_bahamas_country">"\t\tThe BAHAMAS officialy the commonwealth of the Bahamas, is an island country of the  Lucayan Archipelago.\n Picture prfect beaches make the Bahamas a popular destinationfor millions of tourists every year , especially Americans and cruise ship visitors. There are a huge range of historical, cultural and natural attractions in this country,but like most islands in the Carribean, the Bahamas are an expensive destination.\n\n"
        <b>Language</b> : <i>"The official language of the Bahamas is English. Many residents speak the Bahamian dialect.\n\n"</i>
        <b>Culture</b> : <i>"In the less developed outer islands (or Family Islands), handicrafts include basketry made from palm fronds. Junkanoo is a traditional Afro-Bahamian street parade of 'rushing',music, dance and art held in Nassau (and a few other settlements) every Boxing Day and New Year's Day\n\n"</i></string>


<string name="country_tips">"<b>TYPICAL COSTS</b>\n"
    <b>Accommodation</b> - <i>Lodging is expensive.There are very few hotels, but there are resonably priced guest houses and budget hotels with ensuite rooms for around 65 BSD per night.For the best value ,check out Airbnb where you can rent either a spare room or an entire place from a local. Often times these are located in central neighbourhoods or right on the coast at a much better cost per night than a hotel.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Food</b> - <i>"You'll pay around 8 BSD for fish, a side dish and a dessert, which is fairly reasonable for local fare. However,most restaurnts also specialize in American and British meals tha can cost between 17-25 BSD a plate.There is often also a compulsary service charge of 15% on your bill, so keep in mind as you settle a check.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Transportation</b> - <i>"If you are staying in Freeport or Nassau , a minibus trip for 1.25 BSD is the cheapest way to get around,but they stop running at 6 pm. Another option is the wildly popular Water-Taxi that runs every hour for 6 BSD from nassau to Pradise Islands. In terms of inter-island travel, there are frequent and affordable mail boats going fromNassau to the outer islands that cost about 45 BSD each way, but plan accordingly because these can take anywhere from 12-48 hours and offer litte in the way of modern conveniences.Inter-Isalnds flights(via Bahamas Air or other local carriers) are a much more efficient option, and if you buy head of time, the fare usually won't break the bank.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Activities</b> - <i>"Snorkeling, diving, swimming with dolphins, and fishing trips can all easily creep around 150 BSD each, but are an incredible way to experience the islands if you have the budget.Other inland activiies, such as the Pirates of Nassau Museum and the Garden of the Groves on Grand Bahama, are much more reasonable, about 13-15 BSD.\n\n"</i>
    <b>MONEY SAVING TIPS</b>\n\n"
    <b>Nightclub Passes</b> - <i>"Many hotels and even taxi drivers will sell you a 5 BSD pass to get into the clubs around town at a discount. This is a particularly good value if you are visiting on a weekend when cover charges may be 50 BSD at a swanky spot.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Drinking Rum</b> - <i>"Alcohol is expensive in the Bahamas-a case of imported beer can cost around 50 BSD! The exception to this rule is rum or local beer, Kalik or Sands.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Bike</b> - <i>"For around 20 BSD a day,renting a bike offers a good alternative to using taxis to get around. Roads in the Out Islands may not be as well cared for, but you'll rarely come across a stop light or more than a handful of cars.\n\n"</i></string>

    <string name="must_visit_country">"<b>Top Things to See and Do in the Bahamas</b>\n"
    <b>Eleuthra</b> - <i>"If you wamt to escape the mass tourism of Freeport or Nassau, then visit Eleuthra islands. The dozens of beaches here are amazing,and the Current Cut is one of the most famous diving spots in the country. Get swept away with schools of stigrays, mako sharks, and reel fish as the current carries you along. In addition to spending time on the phenomenoal beaches,take a scenic drive through the island and experience the vibrant expat life. Make sure you go to Tippys for nightly music, great drinks, and some of the most affordable food on the island.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Harbour Island</b> - <i>"Just north of Eleuthra , Harbour island is a tiny spot filled with some really nice resorts and beaches. The island is so small, people drive around in golf carts(who wouldn't be into that)and while it may be lot more expensive than other parts of the Bahamas,if you want an upscaale place for a holiday, this is it. To save a bit of cash, considerr staying on Eleuthra, and coming to visit for a day.\n\n"</i>
    <b>The Tounge of the Ocean</b> - <i>"The Tounge of the Ocean is an oceanic trench that runs along the lenth of Andros Island Coast. The wall of the trench leads to an almost 6000 feet drop to the sea bed where divers get up close and personal with reef sharks as they swarm in to feed.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Pirates of Nassau</b> - <i>"Pirates of Nassau is a meuseum dedicated to showcasing the history of piracy on the island. The building is huge and in it you'll walk around a pirate ship, visit the dungeon, and experience the folklore surrounding the Pirates' legacy.This is one of the most prestigious , luxorious and expensive hotels in the world. if you can't afford to stay here, you can use the activities within the resort. The Aquaventure Waterpark has 11 pools, huge water slides(including a Mayan temple themed one which tunnels trough a shark pool), river rapids, and rock climbing.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Garden of Groves</b> - <i>"Located in Freeport on Grand Bahama Island, this 12-acre eco-tourist attration is home to alligators, exotic birds, 10,000 different spicies of plants, four waterfalls and dozens of lakes. Admission is 15 BSD with a guided tour.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Junkanoo</b> - <i>"If possible try to visit Bahamas in late December or early January- every Boxing Day and New Year's Day, Bahamians celebrate their national festival, "JUNKANOO". brass bands, drums, cow bells and whistles provide the soundtrack for thousands of people dancing in the streets.If you can't be there for the main festival, there is a mini festival held in June.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Lucayan National Park</b> - <i>"This 40-acre is home to the world's largest underwater limestone cave system - however, it is only accesible to experienced divers. For everyone else, there are various hiking trails and wind all throughout the pine forest and along Gold Rock Beach.\n\n"</i>
    <b>Fort Charlotte</b> - <i>"This fort from the 1780's has a large moat, canons, hidden passageways and dark dungeons to explore. Those intersted in history will really enjoy this attraction just off the beaten path...\n"</i></string>

    </resources>
